♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
[in English] Today is the day you die.
[in English] And I'm a man of my word!
[Uno, in English] Sir, I have the keys
of the bait vehicle.
[in English] I'll be approaching
in 20 minutes or less.
[Olga] I know how to fight.
- Okay.
- Huh?
Not that you asked,
but I guested as a goon
in Hearts on the Badge.
Through the main entrance!
Where's your helper?
He said it's his birthday.
[goon 1] It's not Jaymar's birthday today.
PREVIOUSLY
[in English] I'm going to execute
both of you in front of the camera
and send it to the armed forces.
[in English] So that they'll know
that I am serious.
[Paldo] Atoy is family.
Now he needs help,
will you all be cowards?
All right, let's fight!
- Charge!
- Charge?
- Let's go! All right!
- Charge!
[clamoring]
All right, all right!
Brad, I'll take over. You go outside.
[thumping and swishing]
[grunting and groaning]
[Uno] No visual of Padua.
- [gunshots]
- [in English] But I'm under heavy attack!
I need immediate backup.
[gunshots]
[Lily] Atoy, what now? Where do we go?
[Atoy] We'll find another way. Let's go.
You think you can escape?
- [thuds]
- [groans]
[grunting and groaning]
[thumping and thudding]
[Ame] That's why you're not Atoy's child!
You probably got that attitude
from your real parents!
[Janine] You're my mommy, right?!
Janine, let's talk first.
[in English] No!
[music swells]
Sister Ame, you should have
controlled yourself.
Because I still feel sorry for Janine.
I'm sorry.
I just couldn't control myself.
She's so annoying.
But fate really plays differently,
doesn't it?
Before she teased you
for not having parents.
In the end, it's her who doesn't have one.
[Ibyang] Janine.
[melancholic music playing]
Janine.
[in English] It's okay.
Ibyang, leave her alone for now.
I want to comfort her.
I want to tell her
everything will be okay.
Because
I know the feeling of having no parents.
[sobs]
[sobs] Thank you.
You're really so kind.
You have such a beautiful heart, Ibyang.
Aunt Audrey, what about you?
Are you okay?
Because surely it hurts
to hear that Janine
isn't really your child.
You know,
you might be the first person
to ask me how I am.
[in English] Thank you.
[in English] I've been better.
[sobs] But didn't you say…
everything will be okay?
[melodramatic music playing]
[Ame] Audrey.
Audrey, I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Don't worry about it, Ame.
Maybe
fate found a way for Janine
to learn the truth.
[music fades]
[breath quivers] I just hope…
Atoy and I will be able to find
our real daughter.
[melodramatic music playing]
Don't worry.
You'll find her too.
You and Tatoy will have a complete family.
[Audrey] I hope so.
[suave theme music playing]
[clamoring]
- [action music playing]
- Charge! Charge!
- [Paldo] Faster!
- [Emerson] Okay!
- [T-Bak] Wait a minute.
- This is it. This is it.
Let's go.
[music fades]
[gunshots]
[screaming and panicking]
Gunfire! Gunfire!
Gunfire! Gu--
- [gunshots]
- [action music playing]
[gunshots]
Wait!
Why are there guns?!
I can't handle that!
Me too! I thought
it was just fistfighting.
But if there are guns, I can't do it!
- Oh.
- Let's call for backup!
Maybe… Maybe there's
a nearby police station!
[in English] Oh,
there's no police station!
The road is long, and we haven't seen one.
So? We're not charging?
I'm charging.
I don't want anything
to happen to Brother Atoy.
Karla!
- Karla!
- Karla, wait!
[T-Bak] It's dangerous inside!
You could die!
It's okay! I don't care!
As long as my brother doesn't get hurt!
- Bro-
- Brother?
Brother? Wait.
Ouch.
Brother?
Brother?!
Yes, Karla and Brother Atoy are siblings.
Ah! I'll explain later!
For now, I'm going to Brother Atoy!
- Karla! Karla!
- Karla, wait for me!
Gavin!
What?!
Atoy will kill us.
Are we just going to stand here?!
Huh?
The reason we came here is to rescue Atoy.
Do or die!
- Until the end!
- [shouting]
End!
- We'll all charge!
- We'll charge!
- Are you ready?!
- Charge! Charge! Charge!
- Charge!
- Let's go!
Let's go.
- Charge!
- Let's go, let's go!
- Okay!
- Let's go.
Wait. Why does it seem like
no one's moving?
- Uh…
- What's wrong with you? What--
What's this? Am I just hyping myself up?
- Uh, Emerson, you know,
- Huh?
I have a good plan.
- What?
- Here's what you do.
- Go inside.
- Right.
See how many enemies there are.
Right!
Yes, right. I'll check
if we're outnumbered or not.
- Okay.
- Then--
- Just look inside.
- Then?
- Then call us.
- Right! Right!
- Yes. Right, right, right.
Yes. That's good, that's good.
- [overlapping chatter]
- You can do it, Brother Emerson!
You can do it!
We believe in you, Brother Emerson!
Why don't you do it instead?
- Not me, not me!
- I have a stiff neck, huh!
Not me-- Not me, brother!
- I might get high blood too!
- I don't think I can!
Go, Emerson!
- [overlapping chatter] You can do it!
- Yes, you can do it.
- I can do it? I can do it?
- You can do it!
- [cheering] Go, Brother Emerson!
- Go, Emerson!
[cheering] Come on! Go!
- I can't do it! I can't do it!
- [clamoring]
Come with me!
- Oh! Go, go, go, go, go!
- Go now!
- There it is!
- There might be more gunfire!
Brother Emerson!
I don't think I can!
You can do it!
Brother Emerson, don't die!
- Don't meddle!
- He can handle it!
- Your hand stinks!
- [in English] Sorry.
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
Uh, uh…
[foreboding music playing]
- [thumps]
- [grunting]
[gunshots]
[Emerson] Help me!
[grunting] Help!
Help! No, no!
[grunts]
- Help!
- [thumps]
[grunting and groaning]
[thumping and thudding]
[gasps]
- [pants]
- Are you okay, Emerson?
- I'm fine.
- [tense music playing]
Emerson!
- [grunting]
- [gunshots]
What?!
They went there?!
Are they so angry at the world
that they'd risk their lives?!
Maybe they just really wanted to help.
But don't worry.
I already called the police
to follow them.
If I could do something, I'd join them.
But I might get
an arthritis attack.
I'd just be a burden.
I'm not as strong as your child, Cita.
What did you say?!
Karla went with them?!
Son of a thread, this child, really!
Yes. They couldn't stop her.
She said she loves her Brother Atoy.
As if the one in danger
is really her sibling, huh?
Well, Atoy really is her sibling.
My God. I hope they'll be safe.
[dramatic sting]
Um, Cita, please repeat
what you said earlier.
That's it.
Let's just pray for them.
My God. What is this?
- [tense music playing]
- Real sibling, she said?
[music swells]
[music fades]
[rousing music playing]
[gunshots]
- [tense music playing]
- [gunshots]
[heavy breathing]
Atoy! [echoing]
[music swells]
[gunshot]
[sneaky music playing]
[whispering indistinctly]
[gasps]
[quirky sting]
[whispers] You too.
[whispering]
[sneaky music playing]
[quirky sting]
[inaudible] Your turn.
[whimpering]
[whispering indistinctly]
[whispers] You go first.
[whispers] Go ahead.
[tense music playing]
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
- [grunts and groans]
- [squeals]
That's really going to fire!
It will fire!
[T-Bak wails] It will fire! It will--
[T-Bak wailing]
[overlapping chatter]
[grunts]
You jerk!
- [groans]
- I told you it would fire!
You jerk! I was already scared!
- [groans]
- And you still won't stop, huh!
- Ouch--
- Oh!
- Why don't you--
- [shouts]
[clamoring nearby]
[indistinct chattering]
[gun cocks]
- [grunts]
- [screams]
Oh, he's gonna fire it!
- [wails]
- Brother Kurt, stop that!
[gasps]
- [sneaky music playing]
- Put it down, put it down.
[gasping and panting]
No one got hit?
- It was wrong to play
- No one got hit?
with toy guns.
- Let's go there. Let's go.
- [T-Bak panting]
Huh?
That should be fine.
[whimpers]
[indistinct chattering]
[tense music playing]
[gunshot]
[clangs]
- [intense music playing]
- Atoy! [echoing]
[music swells]
[tense music playing]
[gunshots]
[machine whirring]
[music swells]
- [Samir, in English] Let's go, let's go.
- Distract them.
- Okay.
- [Samir, in English] It's time
to meet your maker.
Hey, American!
Look here!
Put Brother Atoy down!
[speaks in Russian] Shut your mouth!
[Karla] Put him down! What?!
You won't?!
1v1, come here! Hey!
Go, Gavin! You can do it!
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[Karla] Put Brother Atoy down! Okay!
Go, Gavin! Go! You can do it!
- [grunts]
- [Karla] Gavin! Be careful!
[Karla grunts]
[Karla gasps]
[grunts and groans]
[Karla] Gavin!
[metal clangs]
[music fades]
[panicking]
Brother Emerson, are you okay?
- [shushing]
- They didn't hurt you?
Hey! You're too noisy!
- [shushes]
- [shrieks]
Don't be noisy.
- Don't be noisy.
- [Jona] Emerson!
- [screaming]
- Emerson!
[shushes] You're too noisy!
Hey. Don't be noisy.
Someone-- Someone's chasing me.
- They're chasing me.
- Another one?
Yes. Come here. They have guns! Let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
There are many of them.
There are many of them. Let's get out!
Here, this way!
[action music playing]
- [music fades]
- [gun cocks]
Alcaraz.
Good to see you alive, sir.
Thank you. Where's Lily?
[footsteps approaching]
She's Lily.
She's the decoder.
Atoy, thank you.
Thank you, all of you.
[in English] Good job, Alcaraz.
We need to secure Lily.
She might be targeted again.
I'll take care of Lily Santiago, sir.
[Atoy, in English] Okay.
What about Samir?
He escaped.
So, you should call
Colonel Mercado immediately.
Tell him about Samir
and about the ambassador of Zahran.
- [in English] On it, sir.
- [Atoy, in English] Okay.
[pensive music playing]
Good thing you're safe, Brother.
[Uno, in English] Good job.
[Atoy] Wait, little sister.
How are you? Were you hurt?
[Karla] Not really.
[Atoy] Hmm?
[sighs] How are you?
I'm okay.
Are you okay, Gavin?
You had to tag along.
I just wanted to help.
But I'm fine.
'Toy!
- 'Toy.
- Paldo.
Atoy.
- [man] Brother Atoy.
- [T-Bak] Hi, brother!
Oh? Ha--
What are you doing here?
Atoy, huh. Are you impressed?
See? We defeated the enemies.
- [chuckling]
- We-- We toppled them.
We just got lucky!
What-- What are you doing here?
What if something happened to you?
What if one of you died?
Ouch. We got scolded.
No. Of course, I'm just worried.
I don't want anything bad to happen to you
because you're my responsibility.
I don't want anything bad
to happen to you…
Of course, I love you.
[teasing]
So, you love us, Brother Atoy!
Of course.
You love us, right?
Of course, you're my family.
[teasing]
Group hug! Group hug!
[whooping]
[T-Bak] Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
[suave theme music playing]
Godmother?
- [Olga] Atoy! Atoy! Atoy!
- Ibyang--
- [Atoy] Oh?
- [squeals]
[Atoy] Olga.
Good thing you're safe.
Uh, uh… What are you doing here?
Eh, eh…
I was supposed to join the rescue for you
at the junkyard,
but Uno…
[sighs]
He's terrible company.
He sent me away!
I was all ready to save you.
It's better you didn't.
You might have gotten hurt.
Oh, thank you.
Eh, are Ibyang and the others here?
Where are Godmother Cita and the rest?
Did you see them?
Ah, no. No one's here.
They're at the church.
Church?
- Oh, all right. Thank you.
- Oh. Wait, wait, Atoy. Hold on.
Um…
[sharp exhale]
- [Atoy] What?
- Here it is.
Hold on tight.
You might not be able to handle it.
Why? Did something happen?
Eh, no. Nothing.
[Atoy] Oh?
Don't-- Don't worry. It's good news.
- [in English] Promise.
- Mm-hmm.
‪[Olga sighs]
Uh…
[mellow music playing]
[Olga] Ibyang made that.
She told me
that when I return, we'll be whole again.
Oh.
[Olga] But…
I don't deserve that.
Why not?
Oh, isn't it…
You're her mother, right?
Oh, why-- why would you say that?
[music fades]
You're Ibyang's real father.
She's your child, Atoy.
[music intensifies]
What?
Me?
What are you saying?
What do you mean, my child?
Are you kidding me?
- Because Janine is my child.
- No. Atoy, I'm sure.
I'll explain everything to you.
- Janine isn't your child.
- What do you mean Ibyang-- Ibyang--
Audrey herself told me.
[sentimental music playing]
[car blips]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[Audrey] Ah, Olga?
Who's this?
It's Audrey.
I got your number from Miss Cita.
She said you're with those rescuing Atoy.
Ah, yes. I'm with Uno
and the extraction team.
[Audrey in English] I just
want to wish you well.
[in English] Please bring him back.
I need Atoy.
We need to find our child.
Wait.
Isn't Janine your child?
Before we came here,
I found out Red deceived me.
My brother was the one searching
for our missing child.
The child they introduced to us was fake.
Only a few of you know
that Janine isn't really my child.
But Atoy also needs to know the truth.
[sentimental music playing]
Atoy, you're Ibyang's father.
And Ibyang needs to know all about this.
[in English] Glory be to the Father,
and to the Son, and to the Holy Spirit.
[in English] As it was
in the beginning is now,
and ever shall be, world without end.
Amen.
[light music playing]
Tatoy?!
[sentimental music playing]
[music fades]
Tatoy.
You're back!
Thank you, Lord!
Thank you, thank you!
[sobs]
[sobbing]
Why…
Why are you crying?
Shouldn't you be
happy?
I'm happy. I'm happy, Ibyang.
[sniffles] There's…
There's…
[sniffles] There's something
I brought for you.
[Ibyang] Why do you have that?
[Ibyang] I gave that to Mama Olga.
Eh, Olga gave it to me.
She admitted the truth to me.
That she isn't your real mother.
She only pretended.
Huh?
[sobs] Don't worry about that.
[sniffles] She also
told me the truth, Ibyang.
She told me who…
who your real parents are…
and who your real father is.
What do you mean?
[sentimental music playing]
Whoever holds this…
will make you happy
because he is your family.
[music swells]
You're my family?
[music fades]
Yes. Yes, Ibyang.
[sobbing]
You're my father?
- [Ibyang sobs]
- Me.
[sentimental music playing]
- [electronic blipping]
- [tense music playing]
May you be given a long time
to be with them.
I need your help.
Your new mission.
The corrupt mayor
who is the bagman of senators.
[Mercado] You need to find him.
[Siony] We really need to celebrate this!
[Siony] Not just Atoy's safety,
but also, the safety of Tabang Lupa!
- Exactly!
- [cheering]
- I have an idea!
- [Nestor] What?
[T-Bak] Boodle fight!
[Atoy] Oh? What's happening?
[Emerson] Hey! Look, Atoy is here!
Atoy! Atoy! Atoy! Atoy!
Oh, there. That insect
on your face is gone.
[REd] Don't move too much.
I'll have a hard time killing you.
Insect?
Yes, like a green firefly
that keeps moving.
[Peping] You didn't feel it?
‪UP NEXT
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias